menasoftware.com 2012-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Mena Software

  * Home
  * Privacy Policy

#### privacy (at) menasoftware.com

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected by MENA Software LTD through any and all of its portals, games, etc., how such information is used and to whom and under what circumstances it may be disclosed. By using our Portal(s), which is operated by MENA Software LTD you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### 1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

MENA Software LTD. only collects information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") from you when you: (1) register at the Portal; (2) contact us; (3) purchase products and services from us; and (4) participate in our surveys or promotional activities. Personal Information may include the following categories of information: (1) Contact information (name, e-mail address, etc.); Financial (payments) Data (such as your account or credit card information); and Demographic Data (age, location, etc.). When you contact us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups or forums, or otherwise complete online forms or surveys, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. As part of the standard operation of the Portal, we may collect certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type and version, operating system, IP address and the domain name from which you accessed the Portal. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Portal, the areas or pages of the Portal that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Portal, the number of times you return to the Portal and other clickstream information. We may combine the non-personal information we collect from you with your personal information. We may use cookies and Macromedia Flash local data storage to collect the non-personal information described above. We may also use cookies and Macromedia Flash local data storage to: (1) allow you to use the Portal without having to re-enter your user name and password; (2) monitor Portal usage; (3) manage the Portal; and (4) conduct research to improve the content and services we provide. Third parties that advertise on the Portal may also place cookies in their advertisements. You are free to decline using cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Portal or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Check the Help menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. To learn about your preferences with respect to our use of Macromedia Flash local data storage, please visit www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/help02.html. 

### 2\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US

You may access any personal information you provide, correct or modify any such personal information, or direct us to make no further use of your personal information. To do so, please send an email with your request to privacy (at) menasoftware.com.

### 3\. USE OF INFORMATION

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your requests and answer any of your questions regarding products and services; (2) to protect the security or integrity of the Portal and our enterprise; (3) to review Portal usage and operations; (4) to address problems with the Portal, our business or our products and services; and (5) to contact you when necessary; We may also use the information we collect from and about you to contact you with information and promotional materials and offers from our company, as well as from our subsidiaries, affiliates, marketing partners and other third party companies. In addition to the Information collected, you may choose to share information about yourself through other content ("Content"), such as in games or forums. Any information shared with other game and/or forum users is considered public and at your own discretion.

### 4\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

MENA Software LTD may disclose information collected from and about you only to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law. 

### 5\. SECURITY

We have taken all possible and necessary physical, electronic and contractual steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Portal visitors.

### 6\. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

The Portal may contain links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies different from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any site that you may access through the Portal.

### 7\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from when necessary. Relevant changes will be posted right away on our Portal.

### 8\. CONTACT

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or you have reported data privacy concerns and do not feel they have been adequately addressed, you may contact us at privacy (at) menasoftware.com.
